ivrose.com 2017-11-28

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy details the information that IVRose collects, how we use the information, and how we protect it. We never share, sell or disclose users’ personal information without their permission.

## What information does IVRose collect, and how do we use it?

We may collect information generated by your use of our products and services.

### For example:

  * IVRose collects information you provide when you use our products or services. When you register for an account, contact us for assistance or submit an order, we may collect your name, phone number, zip code, address, etc.

  * We also collect data on how you use IVRose products or services, such as which particular products you view or save, and the duration or frequency of the time you spend engaging with our products or services.

### Uses of information:

  * Customizing the display of products to match your interests.

  * Provide products and the best pre- and post-sale services.

  * Give users updates on current offers and services.

  * Send unique content.

  * Ensure network security.

  * Investigate, prevent and resolve illegal activity, or infractions to our Terms of Service infractions or Acceptable Use Policies.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text filed saved on a user’s computer that helps keep records. IVRose uses cookies so that our systems can recognize your device. This allows us to provide unique service, such as saving products in your shopping Shopping Cart between your visits to IVRose. The information we store in cookies is not linked to the personal information you submit to our website in any way.

### Payment information

If you make purchases on IVRose products or services, we save information about the transaction. This includes your payment information, meaning credit card, debit card or electronic payment information. It also includes other account and authentication information, and billing, shipping and contact information.

### Device information

Depending on the permissions you grant, we gather information pertaining to the computers, phones or other devices where you install, or from which you access our products or services. This allows us to ensure stable usage of our products or services. Device information we collect includes:

  * Information on your machine’s operating system, hardware version, device settings, file and software kinds and names, battery and signal capability, and device identifiers.

  * Device locations, which include geographic locations, such as through GPS, Bluetooth or Wi-Fi.

  * The name of your mobile provider or iSP, browser type, language and time zone, cellphone number and IP address.

### Protection of information

We will not sell your personal information to others. Only under the following specific situations might your information be shared:

  * When we have your permission to share your information.

  * To protect users and the public in case of emergency.

  * To comply with court orders or other legal obligations.

  * To allow for the verification of your identity, and to protect from fraud or identity theft.

### Privacy policy changes

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement from time to time. We will inform you beforehand and allow you to provide feedback on the revised policy.

Last updated: July 27, 2016.

### ADVANCER LTD

Third Floor 207 Regent Street W1B 3HH UK
